Dmitry Khorkin

Github | in LinkedIn | ✓ Mail | ✓ Telegram

SUMMARY

Male, 26 y.o. I have 6+ years of programming experience in different domains. I'm constantly learning. I have a strong scientific background, extensive knowledge in a wide range of technologies, includes computer science, machine learning and web. I love to solve complex problems and explain it by using cool visualizations. I love to build wonderful products with people for people

WORK EXPERIENCE

Evidently AI, Software Engineer

- Led UI development of two related projects: evidently open source library (demo website, github) and evidently cloud (from scratch)
- Accelerated the initial loading of the pages by eliminating network waterfall
- Improved reliability and time of developing new features by implementing custom process of synchronization backend api and client api from scratch
- Improved testing process by creating e2e tests via playwright

Stack: React, MUI, Python, Docker, Github Actions

INPoint LLC, Software Engineer

3.25 years: March 2020 - April 2022, Nov 2023 - May 2023

1+ year: September 2023 - Present

- Developed the backend of Ommie, a minimalistic social network to share inspiring personal stories.
 Stanford writes about us
 - Stack: AWS, S Node.js, MySQL
- Helped to migrate polaris adventures's website from vanilla React (spa) to Remix (ssr) framework. Implemented session functionality. Accelerated the initial loading of the pages (LCP and other metrics) by ~ 2.14 times
 - Stack: AWS, & React, ARRIVER Remix, ARRIVER Redis, BROWN REDISCRETE, BROWN REDIS
- Integrated the CRM system into the bank's existing business processes. Managed the release process.
 Communicated with many teams, includes front/back development, devops, and security. Created the prototype to automate the process of copying and creating a complex CRM's data model based on the DFS algorithm, which saved ~3 days for each deployment on new environment
 Stack: ♦ Django, Python, Node.js, ••• Kafka, Docker, PostgreSQL
- Developed backend of Etra's web platform to automate the selection of heat exchangers, including the core of the system: algorithms for the heat calculation. Communicated with customer engineers in order to map physics they understand to algorithms and code. Developed the entire infrastructure, custom backend & frontend deployment systems

Stack: SelectEl, Node.js, Python, MySQL

UNN, junior researcher

September 2019 - August 2022

Researcher at Department of Control Theory and Dynamic Systems. I have expanded the boundaries of human knowledge about the synchronization process in the field of nonlinear dynamics. Several of my works were published in Q1 journals (see the 'Publications' section below)

Some presentations about my work: Bachelor: english/russian thesis. Master: english/russian thesis

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022 ML developer & partly big data infrastructure at MSc equivalent vandex school of data

2020 - 2022 Master's Degree with honors at UNN, itmm, Artificial Intelligence (GPA: 3.77/4.0)

2016 - 2020 Bachelor's Degree at UNN, itmm, Applied Math and CS (GPA: 3.68/4.0)

SKILLS

Programming languages: is javascript/typescript **?** python, **!>** C/C++, **!>** golang, **!>** haskell (a bit)

SSR: \Remix, Front: \rightarrow html/css, \React, \rightarrow Mui, Back: \ Node.js, \rightarrow \right Web:

Express

Git, Docker, Node.js, Github Actions Tools:

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, S3, Redis Storages:

Computer Science: ⟨/> Algorithms, ⟨/> Operating Systems Internals, ⟨/> Concurrency ⟨/> Asyn-

chronous programming, Distributed Systems (fundamentals)

Pet-projects

Vectorfields Deployment, Source code

Visualization of 2D vector fields in browser

Source code Rotary States

The minimalistic library for finding rotational modes in ODE systems

Source code JS Promises

Implementation of promises in javascript

See all projects on my Github

Publications

Khorkin, Dmitrii S et al. (2020). "Phase control for the dynamics of connected rotators". In: Automation and Remote Control 81, pp. 1499-1506. URL: https://doi.org/10.1134/S0005117920080111.

Khorkin, Dmitry S. et al. (May 2021). "Synchronization structures in the chain of rotating pendulums". In: Nonlinear Dynamics 104.3. URL: https://doi.org/10.1007/s11071-021-06419-x.

Munyaev, Vyacheslav O. et al. (June 2021). "Appearance of chaos and hyperchaos in evolving pendulum network". In: Chaos: An Interdisciplinary Journal of Nonlinear Science 31.6. URL: https://doi.org/ 10.1063/5.0044521.

See all publications in LinkedIn's publications